To configure our time or for PWI.
I'm going to create a new project.
You project over here.
Or select my brought over here.
ASTM 32.
Four one one.
So let's let it pan out or come over here.
Claire Penult.
So basically, GWM is an output, will you speed up your home to drive things like servo motors, DC
Motors and even LCD?
So when we set a pin, when we set it up to him, he has to be connected to a pin such that the output
that we want to drive can be connected to that pin.
So if we want the pin that our LCD is connected to, which is P five, if we want the pin to have Peter
OBM, we have to verify that that pin can also be configured as a timer.
Because Peter B.M. is a timer.
We use a timer to create P2P.
So Peter five is where the ality is.
If you want to nominate a different pin, certainly you can use a different thing.
But to generate Peter, the PIN has to have a timer capability.
And when we click PE five, we realize that one of the options is timer to channel one.
So I'm going to select this one over here.
So we're going to select five to save us time to Channel one.
And then we're going to perform a well fed, a configuration or click.
Time is over here.
And then time to set a set of other.
And then we can, you know, with a configuration.
So we start off by enabling the clock source.
We're going to use internal clock.
And then the channel we use in the fourth time or two is Channel one.
So we've got.
So like Channel one over here.
Click the dropdown for Channel One.
And I'm going to select Pete OBM Generator, Pete OBM.
What is it?
Pete OBM generation Channel one.
Each one.
Right.
Now we need to set a clock configuration or come to the clock configuration tab over here and over here.
This is the default clock.
When you select nuclear abort in your setup, there's the clock.
You come with.
But my point is the SDM 32 for one one, ASTM 32.
It's written here for one one.
The other versions of SDM 32 F, whether it's the Air Force zero one and that one has a default clock
of 16 megahertz.
Because I don't want us to have any hiccups.
I want people to be able to run this code with the F one one and the F zero one.
I'm just going to set this to.
I'm going to change this to sixteen so that we all have the same clock and you don't need to have issues
because you may have a different clock.
Right.
So it's trying to set it to 16 is searching for the perfect arrangement.
Okay.
Once he says to 16, then everything here becomes 16.
There's one thing I'm going to set APB one per four o'clock here to 216 that will change this.
It's 16.
Okay, I can get 16 for APB, one perfect clock, but the rest change, I'll come back to 16 over here.
I see sometimes you get exactly what you want, sometimes you do not.
16 again.
So this setup looks fine.
We just have to make sure our time up, our timer, um, clocks are the same.
So I have my EPB one time clock, 60 megahertz APB to a time, a clock, 16 megahertz.
I think time or two is connected to a TV one or two.
I don't quite remember.
But we have both of them are 60 megahertz.
So there shouldn't be an issue.
You know how to find this information in the, um, in the user guide.
We saw that already.
So let's move on over here.
We can use one thousand as the pre-schooler 1000.
But to be more precise, because we come from zero 1000 becomes one one one like this because you count
zero one, two, three.
But in order not to confuse you, oh, just per 1000, just know that the more precise way is 1000,
minus one for the count up period.
We can, um, we can put sixteen thousand over here.
So like we explained earlier, you first divide by the pre-schooler and then you divide by the yump
to count up period.
Right.
So next we have to come configure the duty cycle over here.
The word true cycle is now used.
What is used instead is the polls.
We know duty cycle is often written in percentage form.
So what a duty cycle is.
The, um, the percentage of the posts, uh, is the um, basically the duty cycle.
This is our counter period.
If I take this count up period, which is sixteen thousand and I pass sixteen thousand to the polls,
this will mean this is one hundred percent duty cycle.
If I pass half of this value this will mean then it is 50 percent duty cycle.
If I pass a quarter of this value it would mean it is twenty five percent duty cycle so you can pass
one hundred fifty percent or 20 percent.
Well we can start off by just passing 50 percent or pass eighty thousand here like this so we can go
ahead and January type project or click over here.
General Project.
I'll give it a name.
Time Paedo p.m..
And also like to my to chain steam theory to cube idea and then generate code over here.
Click here to open the project.
So there's a project of finished the cleanup.
So all we have to do is start our timer with Peter.
You.
Come down here and call the function hall.
I'm a school teacher.
I am on a school.
Start learning to bracket of a sudden it's time to learn.
Then we passed the Cherno TMM channel to Channel One is what we use and channel on a school one like
this.
Okay, so we can build our project or click over here to build.
There is an arrow here.
This function is wrong.
It should be whole time paedo p.m. start.
So I have to put Pedo Beom over here.
Let's build again.
Click over here to build.
It's built successfully.
Let's debug and click over here.
Okay, click here to run.
And as you can see, the lady is totally.
Right.
So it's toggling based on the.
Pete OBM duty cycle in frequency.
So this or the rest.
If you have any questions, just let me know and I'll see you later.